One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Gatz
H-He did it!
He really took down Doflamingo!
He did it!
Dressrosa is saved!
By a rubber ball!
No, he isn't just some rubber ball.
According to King Riku, he is...
the pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
No, wait a minute...
His face looks scarier, and his body's rounder than the guy in the newspaper.
Is that really him?
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?
Huh? Yeah.
I heard he's like an eight-meter tall monster.
This guy's four meters at most.
Then he's a fake?
Hey, rubber ball. Are you really the Straw Hat?
You guys're bugging me!
Why do you keep bouncing up and down?
Can't you stop?
Nope.
Hey, what was that?
I just heard something loud!
Viola?
Straw Hat...
...won!
Really?!
Amazing!
What destructive strength!
There's no way he's still alive!
Hey. Look up, in the sky!
No good!
The bird cage isn't gone!
Dammit! Just one more strike!
Rubber...
Hey, what's the matter, Straw Hat Luffy?
Jesus Burgess!
Why was he here at the Palace?!
You're kidding me!
He jumped down!
I can't believe how far he can jump!
Hello, Sabo-kun?
Come in! Hello?!
That Straw Hat bastard's half-dead!
Now's my chance!
That's...
The captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's pirate crew...
"Champion" Burgess!
Just you wait!
I'll kill you, then rob you of...
the Rubber Fruit!
Are you okay?
Don't!
Don't just walk right up to him. He's a pirate too!
You never know what they're thinking.
What a terrible thing to say!
He fought Doflamingo for us!
She's right!
At the very least, he's not our enemy.
Still, I can't trust him!
But...
King Riku told us that he's our only hope!
Hey, you! Is the battle over?
What happened to Doflamingo?
Doflamingo is still alive!
Get away from the town!
The fight between the pirates is still going on!
We're gonna get caught up in it! Get outta here!
Even downtown's in danger!
The bird cage is closing in!
There's no place to run!
Min... go...
S-Straw Hat Luffy...
H-he can't fight anymore...
If you go near him, you'll get caught up in their fight and die! Don't get involved!
Get away from the pirate!
Straw Hat the Pirate!
Do you recognize me?
I'm Gatz!
The announcer from the Colosseum, Gatz!
The unknown gladiator, Lucy's true identity...
was you, wasn't it?
Y-yeah...
I thought so!
There aren't many small guys who are that strong!
Doflamingo's on his way!
What are you gonna do about your duel?
Is there anything I can do?
I need ten minutes...
After I use Bound-Man,
I can't use Haki for ten minutes afterward.
B-Boun...
I gotta keep my distance,
but I dunno what he's
gonna do during that time.
If I can regain my Haki,
I'm sure I can settle this in one blow!
Then, his horrible reign will be over?
Hey, if we give you ten minutes,
you'll free us from the bird cage, right?!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I promise!
Alright!
Ten minutes!
We'll leave it up to you guys!
You can count on us!
Ten minutes'll pass by in a flash!
You better come back quick
and bring down that damn Dofla, Lucy!
We'll hang in there!
They're all competitors from the tournament!
The ones who wouldn't help you earlier!
Sorry, Lucy!
We were blinded by greed over the bounty on your heads!
We didn't even dream that Doflamingo could be driven into a corner!
Sorry!
As a token of our apology,
we'll put our trust in you and risk our lives!
If we happen to beat him first, sorry!
Thanks for everything, Mr. Heavenly Yaksha!
Why don't you hang out with us for a while?
Here he comes, here he comes!
Kick his ass!
Alright, now's our chance!
The remaining half of you, follow me!
Someone is...
Die, Straw Hat!
B-Burgess?!
Sabo!
Th-That guy...
Oh, the three-star outlaw!
Wh-What?!
The Revolutionary Army's Chief of Staff!
I am Sabo of the Revolutionary Army!
Straw Hat Luffy is my little brother!
Something you want from him, Burgess?
Straw Hat is your brother?
I've heard that somewhere before.
Fire Fist Ace said the same thing, didn't he?
The three of us are brothers.
After the duel on Banaro Island,
you, the Blackbeard Pirates, captured Ace.
That was the trigger for that damnable Paramount War.
Ace lived his own life the way he chose to.
I'm not holding a grudge against you or anything...
but I'm watching Luffy's back from now on!
Remember that!
I have no interest in your relationship to him!
Don't get in my way. I've got no business with you or the Revolutionary Army!
I only have business with...
No business with me? Not even personally?
I see. That was you.
Huh? Flame?
Hey, Luffy.
You've taken some real damage.
Doflamingo's on his way,
and I think my hands'll be full with Burgess.
I'll be fine.
Cats and the others will buy me some time.
It's Gatz!
I'll take down Mingo, no matter what!
You've become so dependable!
Leave this one to me!
Sabo.
You ate Ace's Fruit, didn't you?
I wouldn't let anybody else have it.
It's a memento of him!
That's great!
I'll be taking that power!
Take care of him, Pets!
It's Gatz, and I will!
Galleon...
Lariat!
Burning Dragon Claw Fist!
So hot!
Flame Dragon King!
C-Can't believe it! He blew away a subordinate of one of the Four Emperors!
Powerful! That's what I'd expect from the Revolutionary Army's second-in-command!
As soon as he saw the Flame Fruit's power,
he changed his focus to me.
So his objective is...
...as they say.
He's hunting down Devil Fruit users.
Hey, Lucy! What gives?
I thought you won the competition
and took the Flame Fruit...
The Lucy in the finals wasn't me.
I had somewhere to be, so Sabo took my place.
Oh, so that's what happened.
That's against the rules!
But it all worked out, yeah.
Inheriting your late brother's ability makes for an exciting story.
Well, whatever!
In any case, your recovery is
the only hope Dressrosa has left!
What's with that bastard?
He still has the energy to do this?
Don't hesitate!
We gotta stall him as much as we can!
Annoying weaklings!
I don't need any energy to wipe you out!
Show yourself, Straw Hat!
I'll make you regret everything.
Straw Hat!
That bastard, Doflamingo!
He'll go to any length!
What else is he gonna do?!
First he made the bird cage, and now he's turning the town into strings!
Dressrosa is done for!
Just run! The only way to survive
is to get away from the downtown area!
The whole area's a war zone!
If you get caught up in it, you're dead meat!
I'm not gonna get cut up by that bird cage crap!
Hurry toward the downtown area!
Hey, don't push!
Watch out! I'm gonna get crushed!
I have children!
Stop! Stop!
Hey, why're you running in the opposite direction?! We gotta get to the downtown area!
Downtown's a war zone now!
What?!
What? Then...
Where do we run?!
King Riku, what are we supposed to do?
Armament...
What are you doing, Zoro-dono?
Trying to stop it with your swords?!
It is not something you can stop by merely pushing!
How would you know?
If you have time to jabber on that it's impossible, then gimme a hand, you slow-ass idiots!
It's just one person's ability!
There's no real reason for me to believe I can't stop it!
Shall we, Kin'emon?
We shall!
In Front of the Smile Factory
You ready?!
We are!
The factory's made of Sea Stone!
It can't be damaged!
Let me see that freakish strength of yours!
Alright! Ready!
Push the factory!
Push, push!
Push!
Not yet, not yet! Push, push!
Royal Palace Grounds - Level 2
Zoro and the others are pushing against the bird cage?
Yes.
Is it even possible to stop it?
I don't know. I would have never thought of it.
Roger! That's so like him.
Royal Palace Grounds
South Side
This is the will of the young master!
What?! Get out of our way!
How rude.
Come no closer!
These are the New Royal Grounds!
Only members of the Donquixote Family may enter!
What "Family"? Even the commanders are gone!
But this is the safest place to be! Let us climb up!
Shut up! You damn fools are condemned criminals!
The young master has decreed that
this country will be completely cleansed!
Barrier...
Pistol!
Outta our way, left-overs!
It's the fighters from the Colosseum!
Bartolomeo!
Hajrudin!
Don Chinjao!
Army Commander Kyros is here, too!
How am I able to move?
I'm wondering the same thing.
I didn't think I could move with those injuries.
Don't let your guard down just yet!
By decision of Princess Mansherry,
Dressrosa has been placed on life support!
Life support?
What do you mean, dwarf?
In any case, everybody!
Claw your way to the plateau!
The center of the bird cage is moving this way!
Hooray!
You saved us, Kyros-sama!
Hey, men don't depend on others!
Those of you who are able-bodied, come with us!
Huh? "Come with me"?!
Hey, where're ya going?!
Doflamingo!
If he's not gonna come out,
I'm gonna make him come out!
Hey, that's...
Isn't it moving faster than before?!
No doubt about it!
The bird cage is closing in even faster!
Please save us, Your Majesty!
We're not gonna make it!
Stop it, Doflamingo!
We won't make it!
Push! Put more power into it!
Come on!
Push!
What's the matter?
We're being pushed back!
It's speeding up... Don't let it get the better of you!
Push harder than you've ever pushed before!
Okay!
Push!
Alright, now's our chance to show off!
Yeah!
Come on out, Straw Hat...
Help us!
Hurry! It's shrinking faster!
Three minutes remain until the bird cage reaches the downtown area and the blood bath begins.
You've gotta be kidding!
We won't make it in time!
Four minutes remain until
Luffy's Haki is regained.
This leaves a one minute difference between the moment the bird cage closes completely
and the moment Luffy awakens.